SEAN LAVINE

lavis88@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/seanlavine/ · https://github.com/freewil

Experienced Silicon Valley software engineer with 10 years total working experience and 2+ years working remotely. Looking to join an existing team working remotely from Michigan, either as an infrastructure engineer (DevOps, SRE, etc.) or backend engineer.

I have a variety of experience working as a full-stack engineer, but have spent the last 3+ years primarily working on AWS cloud infrastructure. I'm a curious person and am always open to learning new technologies and tools.

EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2021

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER, INFRASTRUCTURE, DIGIT (REMOTE)

- MacOS build cluster for iOS app (AWS Site-to-Site VPN, CodeBuild, Terraform, Ansible)
- PCI-compliant build and deployment pipelines (AWS CodeBuild, AWS Lambda, AWS ECS)
- Metric instrumentation (Golang, Node.js, MongoDB, Redis, AWS ECS, Datadog)
- Created digitflow developer productivity tool to standardize pull request workflow

2016 - 2018

HEAD OF INFRASTRUCTURE, STOCKPILE

- Migrated company from manual AWS Console management to Terraform
- MySQL bin-log investigation to repair replication
- Introduced error aggregation / monitoring via Sentry
- Improved monitoring and alerting with SumoLogic and CloudWatch
- Technologies: Java, MySQL (RDS), Node.js, Lambda, Kinesis, DynamoDB (MongoDB), Angular.js, Chef/OpsWorks, SQS, CloudWatch, Sentry

2012 - 2015

CO-FOUNDER AND CTO, VAURUM

- Built secure platform to power escrowed OTC block trades for bitcoin
- Total amount raised: \$13 million
- Technologies: AWS, Node.js, Redis, Angular.js, PostgreSQL, Docker, Co-location with Xen Hypervisor

EDUCATION

2010

BS, COMPUTER SCIENCE, WESTERN MICHIGAN UNIVERSITY

Excellence in Computer Science (Colonel Charles E. Bayliss Scholarship), Dean's List, High Honors